regis.edu 2008-12-17

# Regis University

Regis University (“Regis”) is committed to respecting your privacy. This policy is available on the Regis homepage and at every point personally identifiable information is requested. Regis may revise this policy at any time. Any changes to the policy will be posted with other policies within the University portal, called INsite (insite.regis.edu).

This policy does not apply to practices of companies that Regis does not own or control, or to persons that Regis does not employ or manage. 

### Personal Information:

For purposes of this policy personal information is information which is unique to you and by which you can be identified (including, but not limited to, your email address, name, address (work or home), telephone numbers, social security number, credit card numbers, bank account numbers).

### Information Collected:

When you visit any Regis website, Regis does not automatically collect or store personal information. Any data collection performed is for the purposes of aggregate analysis of site usage, and is not recorded in a manner that allows tracking of individual identity. Examples of data collected include: 

  * The date and time of a visit
  * The pages visited 
  * The address of the website from which a visitor came

This information is used for statistical purposes and to improve our services.

Although Regis does not require you to provide personal information when you visit its web site, in order for Regis to respond to a request of yours, or in order for you to avail yourself of Regis services, you may be asked to provide personal information. You can choose not to provide such information, but if you do so Regis may not be able to respond to your request. The personal information you provide shall be used only to fulfill the stated purpose of your communication or participation. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure: 

Regis does not share or disclose personal information except as described below: 

  * Regis will send personally identifiable information about you to others when  1. | it has your consent to share the information;  
---|---  
2. | it is necessary to provide the service you requested (e.g. banks and credit card processors to the extent necessary to deliver payment and/or billing services);  
3. | it believes release is appropriate to comply with applicable laws or regulations; or to protect rights, property or safety of Regis, its employees, users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  

### Information Security:

Regis uses security measures to protect against the unauthorized release of or access to personal information. However, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to or from Regis via its web site or email cannot be guaranteed. Regis has no responsibility or liability for the security of information transmitted through the Internet.

To the extent hyperlinks are utilized to access other sites, be aware that those sites are not controlled by Regis and are not subject to the Privacy Policy. You are subject to those sites’ privacy policies when you leave Regis site. Regis recommends that you review the privacy statements of web sites to which you choose to link.

### Consent:

Your use of Regis online services amounts to your consent to the collection and use of the information by it. You have the right to access the personal information which Regis has collected about you. You also have the right to modify any errors contained in that information. 

_Approved July 10, 2008  
Allan L. Service, Provost and Vice President for Academic Affairs_

Top of Page     Printer Friendly Page
